Guide to the Walter Chauncey Camp Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1875 - 1925; Series I; 13 linear feet (31 boxes)
  - American Defence Society, Inc., 1916 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Golf, 1900, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Institute of Banking, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Intercollegiate Football Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Includes a copy of the constitution.
  - American Intercollegiate Football Rules Committee, 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - American Intercollegiate Football Rules Committee(*), 1905-1910 (Box 1, Folder 25-32)
    Includes the 1925 changes in football rules, minutes of committee minutes, and interpretation of rules..
  - American Intercollegiate Football Rules Committee(*), 1911-1923 (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
    Includes report of the committee to the NCAA and a list of football officials.
  - American Intercollegiate Football Rules Committee: Tributes, [1916?] (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Includes Committee tributes to Walter Camp when he wished to retire from the committee but was persuaded to continue.
  - American Legion, 1919,1923-1924 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - American Line, 1899 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - American Magazine, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American Motion Picture Corporation, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American Olympic Committee, 1920,1922 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American Peace Society, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American - Scandinavian Foundation, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American Sports Publishing Company(*), 1894-1924,undated (Box 2, Folder 38-45)
  - Ames, James Barr(*), 1890-1895,undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Ames, Knowlton L., 1899,1913 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Amherst College, 1884,1894,1903-1906 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Anderson Club, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Anderson, E. H., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Anderson, H. M., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Anderson, W., [1901?] (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Anderson, William Gilbert(*), 1917 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    See also: box 30, folder 823
  - Anderson, W. J., 1904 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Andrews, Alfred C., 1922 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Andrews, Launcelot W., 1900 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Andrews, L. H., 1911, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Angell, Frank, 1896, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Appel, Joseph H., 1892 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Appleton (D.) & Co.(*), 1906-1908 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Appleton (D.) & Co.(*), 1909-1921 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Appleton, Robert
    See: box 17, folder 482
  - Armstrong, H. M., 1916 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Armstrong, Mary E., 1921 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Armstrong, Richard, 1900, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Arnett, W. F., 1916 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Arnold, Edwin, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Arnold, Lawrence, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Aschermann, J., 1917 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Asendorf, George, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Ashley, George H., 1900 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Associated Press(*), 1899-1917 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Association Men, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Association of Army & Navy Stores, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Association of Colleges & Preparatory Schools, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Association of National Advertisers, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Astor, John Jacob, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Atherton, Frederic, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atherton, G. Edward, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Athletic World, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atkins, A. L., 1896 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atkinson, H. M., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atkinson, W. A., 1893,1895 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atlanta Journal, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atlantic City Country Club, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atlantic Union, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atterbury, W. W., 1917 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Auburn Athletic Association, 1915, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Aubut, Oscar C., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Auchincloss, Hugh D., 1889 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Automotive Industries, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Ayrault, Guy, 1901, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Babbitt, James A.
    See: box 1, folder 24
  - Bachman, DeForest L., 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Bacon, B. W., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Bacon, Rebekah G., 1900 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Bacon, Robert, 1894, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Bacon, Thomas R., 1892, 1894-1895, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Badger, Richard G., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Badger, Walter Irving, 1882, 1889, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Badgley, H. H., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Baer, John Millis, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Baillie - Grohman, W. A., 1900 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Baird, Charles, 1905-1907 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Baker, Alfred T., 1888, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Baker, Eugene V., 1892-1894, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Baker, Fred, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Baker, Newton D.(*), 1917-1918, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Baker, Ralph, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Baker, Rhodes, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Baldridge, H. Malcolm, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Baldwin, James, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Baldwin, Roger S., 1893 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Baldwin, Simeon E., 1905 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Ball, Arthur F., 1916, 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Balliet, A. J., 1893-1894 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Bamberger, Simon, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Bancroft, Cecil F. P., 1894, 1902, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Bancroft, Wilder D., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Bangs, Francis S., 1894, 1901-1902 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Bankart, Laurence H., [1919?], 1919 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Bannard, Otto T., 1892, 1903, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Banta, R. G., 1903 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Barbour, F. E., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Barnes, Charles Wheeler, 1901, 1903, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Barnes, Clarence A., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Barnes, Clifford, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Barnette, A. G., Jr., 1901 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Barnum, Jerome D., 1920 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Barr, C. T., 1916 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Barron, A. M., 1916 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Barrows, J. F., 1915 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bartelme, P. G., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bartels, A. C., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bartholomew, Tracy, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bartlett, Edwin J., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Barton, Herbert J., 1904 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Baseball Magazine (*), 1908, 1911-1912, undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Baskerville, A. H., 1906 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Baskerville, Charles, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Batcheller, Robert, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Bates, R. C., 1915 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Battle Creek Sanitarium, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Baxter, Portus, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Baylies, T. B., 1917 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Bayly, Edward, 1890-1891 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Bayne, Hugh A., 1893 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Beach, Harlan P., 1900, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Beach, John K., 1911 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Beachamp, J. M., Jr., 1910-1911 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Beale, Arthur M., [1894], 1909-1911 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Beale, Joseph H., Jr., 1896-1897 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Bear, Russell W., 1911, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Beattie, W. E., 1891 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Beattys, Frank D.(*), 1889, 1891-1892, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Bechly, F. W., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Beck, C. S., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Becker, A. D., 1918 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Bedford, Edward W., 1908 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Beebe, Krebs, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Beebe, William, 1905-1906, undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Beecher, H. W., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Beecher, Harry, 1889, 1892,1910 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Beeckman, R. Livingston, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Behrendt, Arthur J., 1918 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Belknap, Edwin S., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Bell, John Cromwell(*), 1889-1909, undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Bell Syndicate, Inc., 1920, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Bellamy, David, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Belmont School, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Beloit College, 1893, 1895, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Bemis, Harry H., 1920 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Bemis, John W., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Bender, John R., 1909, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Bender, Russell R., 1904 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Bénézet, Louis P., 1904 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Bennett Publishing Co., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Bennetto, John, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Benscoter, W. A., 1900 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Benscoter, W. E., 1911 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Bent, Silas(*), 1921, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Bentley, Edward M.(*), 1900, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Benton, George W., 1906 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Benton, Samuel H., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Berens, Conrad, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Bergen, John Tallmadge, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Berndt, A. H., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Berrien, Frank D., 1909-1911 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Berry, E., 1919 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Bertron, S. Reading(*), 1900-1903, 1905, 1907, 1909-1910, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Bethany College, [1922?] (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Beyer, Henry G., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Bible, D. X., 1916, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Bicknell, Thomas W., 1902 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Biddle, Anthony J. Drexel, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Biddle, Louis A., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Bigelow, Poultney, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Bigelow, Walter I., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Biglow, Ray, 1908,1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Bill, E. Cordon, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Billings, Sherrard, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Bisbee, Eugene A., 1910 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Bissell, R. M., 1918 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Black, Alexander, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Black, Clinton R., Jr., 1916, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Black, Jere. S., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Blackwell, Robert W., 1884 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Blagden, Crawford, 1909-1910 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Blake, Anson S., 1892 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Blake, James Kingsley, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Blakeslee, Clarence, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Blakeslee, Theodore R., 1917 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Blatchlee, S. R., 1906 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Bleifuss, W. F., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bliss, C. D., 1893 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bliss, Laurence Thornton, 1894-1896 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bloomer, Ralph, undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Blossom, J. T., undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Blow, Mrs. George P., 1918 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Blue, Rupert, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bocock, Branch, 1909, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Bok, Edward W., 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Boles, E. C., 1911 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Bomar, Mrs. O. E., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Bonbright, William P., 1908 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Bonifield, H. S.(*), 1920-1922 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Bonniwell, Eugene C., 1917 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Boone, O. V., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Boren, W. E., 1911 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Borie, A. E., 1919 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Boston Globe (*), 1899-1911 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Boston Herald, 1891-1893, 1904, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Boston Journal, 1908, undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Boston, News Bureau, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Boston Post, [1906], 1910-1911,1917 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Botsford, Samuel B., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Bourke, C. F.
    See: box 6, folder 162-181
  - Bovard, David, Jr., 1894, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Bovard, Warren B., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Bowdoin College, 1899, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bowen, Raymond B., 1919 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bowles, Ira E., 1892 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bowman, R. E., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bowmar, Stanley, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bowser, Alex J., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Boyce, William, Jr., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Boyd, Frank, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Boyd, W. E., 1892 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Boy Scouts of America(*), 1916, 1919-1920,1922-1924 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Boys' Magazine (*), 1910-1912 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Bradbury, W. F., 1894, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bradford, John M., [1906] (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bradley, E. E., 1902 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bradley, Edson, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bradley, Harvey, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bradley, Robert P., 1889 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bradstreet Company, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Brainerd, Winthrop, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Braman, Frederick L., 1893 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Bramham, W. G., 1903 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Branner, J. C., 1901 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Bransford, C. W., 1917 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Braucher, H. S., 1917 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Braun, Charles B., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Breck, Edward, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Breckenridge, E. L., 1909 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Breckinridge, Henry, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Brennan, John J., 1917 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Brewer, Arthur H., undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Brewer, Judge, undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Brewer, W. A., 1907 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Brewster, G. F., 1900 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Brewster, L. J., 1908 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Brides, Arthur E., [1909], 1911, 1919-1920 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Briggs, Howard D., 1901 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Briggs, L. B. R. (*), 1912-1915, 1920-1921 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Brigham, F. Gorham, 1915-1916 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Brinton, Howard F., 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Britt, Albert (*), 1909-1910 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    See also: box 19, folder 520-523
  - Bromley, Harry, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Bronson, Clarence W., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Brooke, Frederick H., 1899 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Brooke, George H., 1902, 1907, 1916, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Brooks, Alfred H., 1900 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Brooks, Charles F., undated (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Brooks, D. F., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Brooks, James Wilton, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Brooks, Henry Stanford (*), 1890-1896, 1899-1903, 1905-1909, 1918-1920, undated (Box 4, Folder 97-101)
  - Brooks, Lilian (*), 1899-1900, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Brooks, William A., Jr., [1889?]-1916, undated (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Brophy, John D., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Brown, D. E., 1896, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Brown, Elwood, [1912?] (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Brown, Fayette, 1889-1890 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Brown, F. Gordon, 1900, 1902, 1905, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Brown, G. E., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Brown, George T., 1888 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Brown, George V., 1917, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Brown, H. J., 1899 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Brown, Harry O., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Brown, Horace, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Brown, J. T., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Brown, Jamot, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Brown, Lincoln Doty, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Brown, P. G., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Brown, T. H., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Brown University, 1894, 1905, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Browne, Harold F., 1905 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Brownell, Clarence Ludlow, undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Brownell, Holder M., 1881 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Brumbaugh, Martin G., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Brune, T. Barton, 1883, undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Bryan, John H., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Bryan, P. Taylor, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Bryant, C. W., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Bryce, R. B., undated (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Buchholtz, William, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Buckland, Edward G., 1893-1894 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Buckley, George D., 1919-1920 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Buckley, Paul, 1889 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Buel, David, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Bulkley, Jonathan, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Bulleit, L. L., 1922 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Bullock, Walter L., 1903 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Bunker, Caroline Hemenway, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Bunyan, George B., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Burch, Robert B., 1910, 1912, undated (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burchard, R. B., 1891 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burdette, Robert J., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burg, Copeland C., 1915-1916 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burgess, F. B., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burgess, George F., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burket, Harlan F., 1909 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burleson, Albert Sidney, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burnel-Wright, William, Jr., 1892 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burnette, A. G., Jr., 1903 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burnham, Arthur, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Burr, George H., 1916-1917 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Busbee, Perrin, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Bush, Edward W., 1912 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Bush, Gavien A., [1910] (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Bushnell, Sam C., 1909-1910, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Bushnell (Cornelius) National Memorial Association
    See: box 7, folder 205
  - Business Men's League, St. Louis, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Butler, Arthur P., 1889, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Butterworth, Frank S., 1902-1903, undated (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Butts, George W., III, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Buxton, C. B., 1908 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Byrd, Richard Evelyn, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Byrne, Joseph F., 1920 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Cabot, Edward F., 1889 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Cadwallader, Frank I., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Caine, Matthew T., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Calderon, Don Ignacio, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Caldwell, John H., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Calhoun, Gouverneur, 1890-1892 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Calhoun, Henry W., 1896 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - California, University of, 1894, 1910, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Callender, James H., 1911 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Callisher, Henry, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Calnon, William
  - Cameron D. R., 1906 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Cameron, H. A., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Camp, Charles Clark, 1891, 1894, undated (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Camp, E. C., 1920 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Camp, William J., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Campaigne, Caspar C., 1907 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Campbell, Donald Y., 1892, undated (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Campbell, George, 1898 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Campbell, N. Stuart, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Campbell, Raymond, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Canadian Amateur Athletic Union, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Cann, F. H., 1894, undated (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Cann, J. Murray, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Capen, Wallace C., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Capper, Arthur, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Carey, John W., 1899 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Carey, W.(*), 1891-1892, 1894, undated (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Carleton, Guy, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Carlisle Indian School
    See: box 25, folder 701
  - Carney, Earl M., 1902 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Carney, Peter P., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Carpenter, George Albert, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Carpenter, James S., 1903, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Carpenter, Percy R., 1911 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Carrington, John B., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Carroll College, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Carson, E. W., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Carter, George R., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Carter, Walter F., 1902, 1905,1908, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Cartwright, Bruce, Jr., 1910 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Cary, Robert J., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Case, George B.(*), 1904, 1908, 1911-1913 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Castle, E. W., 1911 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Castleman, Frank R., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Cates, John C., 1913, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Catts, Sidney J., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Cauldwell, Thomas W., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Cavanaugh, Frank W., 1912, [1916] (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Cavanaugh, G. H., 1910 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Central Press Association, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Centre College, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Century Magazine (*), 1893-1894, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Century Magazine, 1900, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Century Magazine (*), 1909-1912 (Box 5, Folder 132-133)
  - Century Magazine, 1916-1917, undated (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Cerf, Myrtile, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Chadwick, Charles, 1904, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Chadwick, George B., 1902, 1911-1912, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Chadwick, Henry, 1884, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Bristol, Connecticut, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Cleveland, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Connecticut (*), 1920-1921, 1923, undated (Box 5, Folder 137-138)
    Includes minutes of meetings and copies of a questionnaire of the committee of General Welfare.
  - Chamber of Commerce, Kansas City (Missouri), 1917 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Chamber of Commerce, New Haven (Connecticut) (*), 1909, 1911-1913, 1915-1917 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Chamber of Commerce, New Haven (Connecticut) (*), 1920-1922, undated (Box 5, Folder 140-142)
    Includes minutes of meetings, reports and programs.
  - Chamber of Commerce, Portland (Oregon), 1923 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Portsmouth (New Hampshire), 1923 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Chamberlain, W. I., 1894 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Chamberlin, Burr(*), 1902, 1905, 1912-1913, undated (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Chandler, W. H., 1894, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Chaney, L. W., 1905-1906 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Channing, R. H., Jr., 1894 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Chapin, C. F., 1899, 1908-1911, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Chapin, E. B., 1904 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Chapman, Charles E., 1905 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Chapman, Henry G., 1895 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Chapman, J. L., 1919 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Chapman, Lansing, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Chapman, William L., 1920 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Chappel, F. V., 1909 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Charles, James K., 1892 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Charlesworth, Langdon, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Charnley, Mitchell V., 1923 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Chase, F. L., 1899 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Chase, Irving H., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Chase, Ralph E., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Chatfield, Helen H., 1918 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Cheesman, William S., 1884 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Cheltenham Advertising Agency, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Cheney, Howell, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Chesnutt, Charles, 1908 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce, [1924?] (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Chicago Athletic Association, 1893-1896, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Chicago Daily News, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Chicago Journal, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Chicago Record, undated (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Chicago Tribune, 1899, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Chidley, Howard J., 1923 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Child, Benjamin N., 1897 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Children's Foundation, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Childs, Starling W.(*), 1917 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Christie, Walter M., 1906, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Chrystal, Eugene, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Church, Edgar M., 1894 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Church, James R., 1894 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Civic Federation of New Haven, 1911-1913 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Clark, B. F., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Clark, Charles Hopkins, 1909, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Clark, Horace B., 1910 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Clark, W. A. D., 1910 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Clarke, Benjamin E., 1911 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Clarke, Charles C., Jr., 1903 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Clarke, W. F., undated (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Clarkson, John G., 1893 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Claxton, P. P., 1918 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Cleaveland, Livingston W., 1917 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Clemans, C. L., 1893, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Clemens, S. L., 1902-1903 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Cleveland Advertising Club, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Cleveland (Ohio) High School, undated (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Cleveland Press, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Clevenger, Z. G., 1911 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Clinton, H. S., 1920 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Clinton, Harry Thomas
  - Cobb, J. O., 1905 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Cochems, Edward B., 1903, 1906, 1910, 1920, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 155)